'use strict'

/*
    *** Question data
*/
const QuestionData = [
    {
        questionNumber: 1,
        question: 'Which console has sold the most units to date?',
        answers: ['PlayStation 2', 'Nintendo Switch', 'PlayStation', 'NES'],
        correctAnswer: 'PlayStation 2',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 2,
        question: 'What was the first home gaming console?',
        answers: ['Magnavox Odyssey', 'Atari 2600', 'Atari Pong', 'Coleco Telstar'],
        correctAnswer: 'Magnavox Odyssey',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 3,
        question: 'How many units did the NES sell worldwide?',
        answers: ['61.9 million', '102.3 million', '18.2 million', '54.4 million'],
        correctAnswer: '61.9 million',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 4,
        question: 'Which game was the first to feature the ever popular Mario?',
        answers: ['Pinball', 'Wrecking Crew', 'Donkey Kong', 'Super Mario Bros.'],
        correctAnswer: 'Donkey Kong',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 5,
        question: 'Nolan Bushnell co-founded Atari and developed/founded what popular entertainment franchise?',
        answers: ['ShowBiz Pizza', 'Chuck E. Cheese', 'Dave and Buster\'s', 'None of these'],
        correctAnswer: 'Chuck E. Cheese',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 6,
        question: 'What is \'Nintendo\' reputed to mean in English?',
        answers: ['Gambling is fun', 'Heaven can wait', 'Superior playing cards', 'Leave luck to Heaven'],
        correctAnswer: 'Leave luck to Heaven',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 7,
        question: 'What was the first LaserDisc based arcade game?',
        answers: ['Dragon\'s Lair', 'Astron Belt', 'Space Ace', 'Time Traveler'],
        correctAnswer: 'Astron Belt',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 8,
        question: 'While not the first video game for entertainment, that distinction goes to \'Tennis for Two\', which of these is considered the first widely available video game?',
        answers: ['Pong', 'Computer Space', 'SpaceWar!', 'Space Invaders'],
        correctAnswer: 'SpaceWar!',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 9,
        question: 'Which game was a launch title for the NES?',
        answers: ['Metroid', 'Clu Clu Land', 'Legend of Zelda', 'Tetris'],
        correctAnswer: 'Clu Clu Land',
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 10,
        question: 'Which game console was the first to bring CD-ROM based games to the home?',
        answers: ['PlayStation', 'Nintendo Famicom', 'Sega Saturn', 'Sega CD'],
        correctAnswer: 'Sega CD',
    },
];